Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
The hero's name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He was later hailed as the first Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Sorry, Asta, but if you can't keep up, I'm ditching you.
You should know that's never gonna happen!
You're just a human, yet you're using Elven and spirit power to fight me.
Monozone, Dark Cloak, Dimension Slash, Equinox!
All dark magic can interfere with the other world! Curse that human!
Right here, right now, I'm going to push past my limits!
This is my limit!
I don't need luck, all of you are full of love
I'll be with you, I'll be with you
Let's die in this world, even I cannot wrap this world
All I need is getting strong, we can catch the game
I can't hide it all, many of us spend it all
We can catch the game, we can catch the game
We can catch the game
Impossible
This can be
Inconceivable
It can be
If I won't have it
You got a problem there, comrade
Don't give me that
Who are you? Tell me
You don't need to know that
It doesn't matter how powerful you are
You've lost this fight and you're about to disappear for good
Farewell, you disgrace
We won!
I'm grateful
That terrible magic
It vanished
Did they stop him?
It looks like somebody beat me to the punch, but I'm glad to see the job got done
You did well, human
Actually the name's Yami Sugihiro
Prickly princess too
For the last time, call me Sharla
Oh no!
His magic's not completely gone
It's consuming everything
This place is about to crumble
We have to get out, now
But what about everyone else?
I think my body is reaching its limit
There's not much time
The light is starting to grow dimmer
What gives?
I feel all creepy crawly
My connection to Lick tells me
The only way out is on the top floor
Let's go!
We can't get up there
If we don't figure this out quick then we're screwed
That key
Lumiere
The light
It's fading
That key
Lumiere
The light
It's fading
This is bad
You guys
Hey it's you
You're all okay
And man talk about good timing
Stop clinging to me like that you idiot
Back off
Sorry
It seems the person I put my faith in was nothing but a pitiful sinner just as I am
Now I must make amends for the wrong I've done
If such a thing is even possible
You two again
Well this guy doesn't speak for me
I've never been wrong once in my life
If you were here you could have at least helped us out
Hey don't you judge me I do whatever I want when I want
There's one more thing I need to do before this is over
What do you know just when I least expected and a boneless hand goes flying by
The little spell of yours might make your body invisible to the naked eye but I can sense your key plain as day
We got you now
It's Captain Yummy
And the Blue Rose Knights Captain
And that guy
He used to lead the Purple Orcas
How dare you treat me like this after all the suffering I've had to endure
Hey wait
You're that jerk who stole my grimoire forever ago
Rev Chi
What the heck are you two clowns doing here
At least we have magic power
How impressive
So many mages with so many different types of spells
I think the clover kingdom is in good hands
Enough chit chat let's get going
Go away
I'll never let you out of my sight again you know
Hands off him little miss five head
Oh
Charmy you changed back to your normal self
That was so cool when you turned all tall and tough before
And your powers were super awesome
Huh
I don't know what you're talking about
I'm sexy taon long-legged 24-7
What?
Wait she didn't notice what happened?
Better question
Why is Charmy here at all?
Cause wherever there's you knowing yummy nummies I'm bound to pop up eventually
Just so you know lady I'm still going to slash you up
What's wrong with this guy?
He's creepy
Settle down
There's no time for idle chatter
Remember
This isn't over yet
We have to stop the elves from destroying the kingdom
They're still being driven by deep-seated hatred
Completely detached from their real souls
There are so many
How can we overpower them all?
I'll knock them out with one good punch
Something tells me she actually could too
Oh man
I won't be able to get to everybody with just one sword
Not to mention my powers running low
Lict is here now
There's a way
William is still lying dormant within me
With his world tree magic
We can gather mana and life force from people all over
To make that happen
We're going to need his grimoire
Take it
This is the one
Valtos
Thank you
It doesn't matter who you are
You're still the person who found me that day and saved my life
Hang on
Are you seeing that?
Yes
Asta
Use that weapon
To destroy me for good
Sure that's what you want?
I've already lived twice now
I have regrets but no fear
After all that I did
I'm not sure this is enough to atone for it
Padre
I'll be the first one to leave then
Forgive me, Lict
Please finish this
I will
In the end, I got to fight alongside Lict and all my friends
That's enough
It's Captain Vongence
Padre
The lonely soul who's been with me ever since I was a child
Seems your rage and suffering have finally reached an end
But
The story's not over yet
This time it's my turn
This mark that was carved upon my face without reason
The curse that brought me so much mistreatment and hatred
Because of it
His warped feelings for the kingdom and the suffering he went through were undoubtedly real to me
This battle happened because I was too weak to believe in Julius's strength
Or in the future I was meant to protect
Therefore
I should be the one who puts a stop to this violence
I'll connect to their souls and tell them the truth
We need to lure the connected souls to the World Tree
And bind them together
Combo spell
Demon dweller sword
Spirit light tree
Now anti-magic wielder
Use the demon destroyer sword
The power of that blade is reaching all of the elves
The power of the rings
The power of the龍
Look up there. That's the magic of the Golden Dawn's captain. Beautiful!
Does this mean they save the kingdom?
I should have known. Apparently the three of us won't be going with you.
See, after we got reincarnated the second time, our souls became bound to these bodies.
There's no way we can go back to our original forms.
I see. That's a shame. After a journey filled with pain and hatred, it'd be nice if we could talk.
But, nothing to be done now. Perhaps there's a reason our destiny's played out this way.
Live on in this world. For all of our sakes.
Goodbye.
Take care.
That figures. We missed each other again.
But if this is what you want, then okay.
I guess I'll live this life to the fullest, no matter how much of a pain it is.
I wish I'd seen my younger brother again.
But I enjoyed fighting with you, Yami Sukihiro.
Well, look at you, Charlotte, turning all nice and honest at the end. That's sweet.
I admit I may be a little awkward, but not as awkward as she is.
I suppose I'd better be going now. I wouldn't want to keep my dear Tetya waiting any longer.
Right.
I'm happy we got to see a glimpse of the ideal future that we'd always hoped for.
Me too.
The elf that's in my body, is he your...
With you here, it felt like I got to fight alongside my son.
Thank you, wielder of the four-leaf grimoire.
May good luck always follow you.
This is yours, right?
Take it.
Actually, the five-leaf grimoire belongs to you now, Asta.
Hold on tight to it.
It will prove helpful on your journey.
Farewell.
And thank you, mages of the Clover Kingdom.
Not so fast!
Hold on a damn second!
Wraith, magic, soul abductor!
I can only use this spell as somebody who's been a part of my life for a long time.
And ironic as it is, you fall into that category.
The body that held Lick's soul has magic in it again?
But wait.
That mana...
Potri?
Am I...
Reborn?
No.
Reanimated.
That body was only a duplicate that Sally created to look like your original one anyway.
I'm sure you'll feel right at home in it.
Hey, what the heck are you doing?
Shut up, would you?
No!
This is...
I, uh...
Look, I don't understand it either, all right?
Anyway...
Lick, or Potri, or whoever!
I'm not just gonna let you disappear, live happily ever after!
No way!
I won't ever forgive what you did!
That's why...
I want you to spend the rest of eternity thinking about all the humans you trampled on, including me!
Uh, hey...
That might come back to bite you later.
Quiet!
Rhaedis, I feel like I should thank you, since you've given me the chance to atone.
Shut your mouth!
I'll have your head if it's the last thing I do.
And until that day, I want you to spend your life in constant fear!
Let's go, Voltos!
Hmm.
Wow.
So, after all that, you didn't even get to go back with Lick like you wanted.
Ain't that just the way.
It's only fair, though.
Raya.
It's you.
I never expected we'd see each other face to face.
Neither did I.
My closest companion, who shares my sin.
There was so much that I wanted to tell you.
But first this, he may not listen, but I owe someone an apology.
I know this is a selfish thing to ask you, but Yami, please take me to see Julius at once.
Of course.
The Wizard King.
The long battle is finally over.
Oh, I've been in so much pain this whole time, I'm gonna die!
Oh, you poor thing, that sounds terrible!
Maybe you'll remember this next time you're about to do something reckless and stupid.
From the bottom of my heart, I can't thank you all enough.
The spell has been lifted, despite that devil's best efforts.
And with another devil's power, no less.
You broke the seal a while ago, and you're just now starting to feel the pain?
Quite impressive.
By the way, Asta, who are those two people?
Who is that man?
I know it sounds crazy, but he almost looks like the statue of the first Wizard King come
to life or something.
Well, I think that's pretty much what happened, actually.
Really?
You were awakened by magic, right?
Oh, man, I can't wait to be a super awesome Wizard King just like you someday!
And guess what else?
That's Nero.
The bird?
Wow, Asta, you must have hit your head pretty hard if you think that.
It's true.
What?
You know...
Dio, I thought you were a pretty cool little bird, but now that I know you can turn yourself
into a human, I think you might be the coolest bird that ever lived!
I didn't transform into a human, I was a human to begin with.
Then why didn't you tell me before?
Because up until the Shadow Palace appeared, I wasn't able to talk.
Now I have a question to ask you.
What makes you think you can ever hold a candle to his highness?
Look, I know we're old pals, but please count that out!
So the spunky, adorable Nero is...
Well, she's spunky and adorable!
Well, to me, Wizard King is nothing but a simple phrase.
But thanks to you and your rival, it's become clear to me that our ideals live on with this
generation as well.
Now then, which one of you will take my place?
Oh, that'll be me, sir!
You're nothing compared to him, Asta.
You're mean!
The time has come.
I don't have enough magic to hold this body together anymore.
My recovery magic can't fix this!
My prince...
Secre.
Or Nero, I suppose.
Will you watch their futures play out?
Watch them make the world better?
For my sake?
I've always been...
Well, um...
I mean...
Anyway...
Let me go with you.
Please, sir.
I gave everything 500 years ago.
I should have died that day.
But then...
You help me protect the future.
Let me go.
Like I said, I can't let you seal off your potential.
I think the path ahead is a bright one.
Both for the magic knights and for the kingdom they'll fight to defend.
I even met my descendants.
I'm happy.
So am I.
Really.
Serving you for so long, it...
It was an honor.
I was honored to have you.
Secre.
Thank you for everything.
You did well.
Goodbye.
Good night.
Bye.
悩まない雨 居場所を示す
足跡はやがて消えてしまうから
The new page is now open
I'm not afraid of
I'm at the top of my head
Just take my hand
I'm living today
I'm waiting for
What?
No way!
Are you Julius?
The long night's finally over
Look at that gorgeous sunrise
It's the new dawn of the Clover Kingdom
Black Clover page 121
Three problems
Damn this old dude's office rocker
This old dude's office rocker